

Profile

I'm a Front End Developer who's aiming to become a Full-Stack Developer. I have worked on many projects. I use effective technologies and standards which usually results in a quality product :).

Enthusiastic and self-taught, willing to learn and develop in the best possible way in new technologies, assuming challenges that allow me to develop professionally, always responsible and committed to my duty.

Along the way I have worked with multiple technologies and programming languages but currently all my focus is on ReactJS and .NET.

Employment History

Frontend Developer, Ecoplast Hart SRL, Hunedoara

JULY 2019 - JULY 2021

- Performing daily administrative tasks to ensure good functionality and coordination of daily activities
- Ensure that website visitors can easily interact with the company website.
- Implementing new features
- Maintaining a good functionality of the systems
- · Updating databases
- Updating the inventory
- Implementing new features

Frontend Developer, Ceeltim, Timisoara

JANUARY 2018 - JUNE 2019

 I was responsible for building web application and implementing visual and interactive elements. I was responsible for building web application and implementing visual and interactive elements.

Education

Front-End Development, Business Academy Aarhus, Århus

AUGUST 2021 - PRESENT

Java Developer, IT School, Timisoara

JULY 2019 - DECEMBER 2019

Modul Pedagogic, Universitatea de Vest din Timisoara, Timisoara

OCTOBER 2019 - JULY 2020

Physical Education and Sport, Universitatea de Vest din Timisoara, Timisoara

SEPTEMBER 2015 - JULY 2019

Kinetoterapie si Motricitate Speciala, Universitatea de Vest din Timisoara, Timisoara

SEPTEMBER 2015 - JULY 2019

Details

https://dani-ispas.com/

Aarhus

Denmark

+45 55225041

ispasdani14@gmail.com

DRIVING LICENSE

В

DATE OF BIRT

14-11-1995

Links

Portofolio Website

Github page

Languages

English

Romanian

Technologies I use

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

ReactJS (focused on)

C# (focused on)

Java

Hobbies

- Ski
- Tennis
- Trekking
- Climbing